Welcome to this task about deciding the
relationship type for different scenarios. We
shall decide for each of these cases whether we've
got an association, aggregation, or composition.
We shall also justify our decision. We shall
choose the strongest existing relationship type.
The first example is a color is in a
painting. We know that color can be
in different paintings. But, of course, the
painting consists of all these colors. So,
it's an aggregation. The important thing
is that it is not composition is because
the colors could also be used in another
painting. That is why it is an aggregation.
The human body consists of organs. In this
case, I think we've got a composition. Because
when the body doesn't exist anymore, then
the organs won't be any more as well.
Only if we consider the case of organ donations,
then could we say it's not a composition. It's
rather an aggregation. Because then the organs
could be transferred to another body and could
be used there. So, the relationship in that case
between body and organs would be an aggregation.
Pictures are stored on the phone.
This would be an aggregation because the pictures
could also be stored on another device. So, it's
not exclusive to the phone. That's why there is an
aggregation here. A university has many teaching
chairs. In this case, it would be a composition
because if the university is closed, then there
wouldn't be any teaching chairs anymore. So,
the teaching chairs exist only because of the
university. And if the university is closed,
then the teaching chairs are closed as well.
The next one is, at a teaching chair,
several persons are working as assistants.
In this case, it's no composition like in
the case before. It's rather an aggregation.
Because after a teaching chair is dissolved,
the persons are still existing and working.
Assistants could work anywhere else. And they are
not destroyed by dissolving the teaching chair.
Then, the room LF233 can be found in the building
LF. This is a composition because the building
consists of these rooms. And if the building
is gone, then the room won't be anymore. So,
if the building is destroyed, then you can't go
to the room LF233 anymore. And that's why this
is a composition. The building LF is part of the
University of Duisburg-Essen. This is rather an
aggregation because the university consists of
multiple buildings. But when the university is
dissolved, then the building will still exist.
It could be part of anything else. Transferred
maybe in housing or into a clinic or something
else. The next one is students attend a lecture.
In this case, the lecture is not really
dependent on the students. And it
also happens if there are no students. It's rather
an association between students and lectures.
The next one, the earth has different continents.
If you think about what happens when the earth is
destroyed, there will be no continents anymore.
That is why we have a composition in that case.
The last one is, a house is placed in a street. In
this case, we could think about how the house and
the street relate. And we think about the house
exists and the street exists. But they are only
connected by the address. The only relation
is the address. It's a simple association.
There are no real dependencies
between the house and the street.
So, that's everything for deciding for
all these examples. Thank you very much.